She felt his warm breath..."
(Leonard:)You will not believe
what Stephen Hawking just said.
PENNY: Get out!
BERNADETTE:
Not now!
(Amelia:)Is the water warm enough?
(Cooper:)Given the fact that you took
the time to build a wood fire,
(Cooper:)draw the water from
the well and heat it,
(Cooper:)it would be rude
to complain.
(Cooper:)But since you asked,
it's a little nippy.
(Amelia:)I can fix that.
(Amelia:)I couldn't help but notice
your unusual undergarments.
(Cooper:)They're not undergarments.
(Cooper:)They're Underoos.
(Cooper:)Where I come from,
they're known as
"underwear that's fun to wear."
(Amelia:)And what's the significance
of the spider?
(Cooper:)Oh, that represents
Spider-Man.
(Cooper:)He does whatever
a spider can.
(Amelia:)There's a lot of rhyming
in the future, isn't there?
LEONARD:
You're right.
(Leonard(in bed):)This is even weirder
than I thought.
(Penny:)You want me to
stop reading?
(Leonard:)Are you kidding?
No, no.
"As he stood for
Amelia to dry him..."
(Amelia:)So, tell me, Cooper...
(Amelia:)are the ways of physical love
different in the future?
(Leonard:)Yeah, okay, I'm good.